Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
McCann-Erickson Audiovisual collection
1980s-1990s and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
McCann-Erickson Worldwide
RL.00863
75 Linear Feet
McCann-Erickson, founded in 1930 from the merger of Alfred Erickson's and Harry McCann's agencies, is one of the largest advertising agencies in the United States. It is part of the Interpublic Group. The McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection spans the 1980s and 1990s and consists of over 700 videocassette tapes of commercials for domestic, international and global advertising campaigns. Also included are tapes of competitor commercials; interviews with agency and industry leaders and marketing specialists; and presentations. Advertisers include: Apple computer; Bayer; Benson & Hedges; Buick; Calvin Klein; Camel (R.J. Reynolds); Coca-Cola; Del Monte; Exxon; Heineken; Kodak; Levi Strauss; Nestlé; Oxo; and Suntory. The bulk of materials consist of advertisements for campaigns in the United States, but Brazil, Japan and Germany are also heavily represented, as are commercials for Europe-wide campaigns. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
3000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed. Where digital use copies are available, they will be identified in the Containers field for that item.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift from William O'Barr in 1994.
Collection Overview
The McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection spans the 1980s and 1990s and consists of over 700 videocassette tapes of commercials for domestic, international and global advertising campaigns. Also included are tapes of competitor commercials; interviews with agency and industry leaders and marketing specialists; and presentations. Advertisers include: Apple computer; Bayer; Benson & Hedges; Buick; Calvin Klein; Camel (R.J. Reynolds); Coca-Cola; Del Monte; Exxon; Heineken; Kodak; Levi Strauss; Nestlé; Oxo; and Suntory The bulk of materials consist of advertisements for campaigns in the United States, but Brazil, Japan and Germany are also heavily represented, as are commercials for Europe-wide campaigns.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged into two Series: Original Videotapes; and Videotape Documentation. Original Videotapes list the videocassettes in numerical order, and provide contents listing where known; Videotape Documentation consists of tape contents lists removed from the cassette cases, along with notebooks containing notes on most of the videotapes--this information has been transcribed into the body of the finding aid in the Original Videotapes series; Original order was maintained. Tapes were sequentially numbered and are housed in numerical order. Some tapes were missing at the time of processing, a fact which is noted in the container list.
Television commercials -- Brazil; Television commercials; Television advertising -- United States; Television advertising -- Japan; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising campaigns; Advertising campaigns -- Brazil; Advertising campaigns -- Europe; Videocassettes; Television commercials -- Japan; Television commercials -- Germany; Television commercials -- Europe; Advertising campaigns -- Japan; Advertising campaigns -- Germany; Cable television advertising; Advertising campaigns -- United States; Television advertising -- Brazil; Television advertising; Television advertising -- Germany; Television advertising -- Europe; Del Monte Corporation; Eastman Kodak Company; Exxon Corporation; General Motors Corporation. Buick Motor Division; Heineken's BierBouwerij Maatschappij; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Levi Strauss and Company; Apple Computer, Inc.; Bayer HealthCare; Benson & Hedges (Firm); Calvin Klein, Inc.; Coca-Cola Company; McCann-Erickson Worldwide; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company; Oxo Limited; Nestlé; Santori Kabushiki Kaisha
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  List of videotapes. Where known, detailed listings of videotape contents have been provided. Arranged in numerical order. Some numbered videotapes were missing when collection was received. These are noted in the container list.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restrictions on Access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to research until digital use copies can be made. Where digital use copies are available, they will be identified in the Containers field.
  - 1. The 20th All Japan Radio & TV Commercial Council (ACC) Film Festival; Excellence Prize 2-2; No. 1 of 4. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 2. The 20th All Japan Radio & TV Commercial Council (ACC) Film Festival; Excellence Prize 2-1; No. 2 of 4. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Kowa/Cabejin Kowa (Box 1)
    - Kowa/QP Gold (Box 1)
    - Sankyo/Lulu Gold A: Dozing (Box 1)
    - SK&F/Contac 600: Neon Sign (Box 1)
    - Lion toothpaste for children: Animals (Box 1)
    - Rhoto/Casilon: Chinese Food (Box 1)
    - Lion/Zact Lion: Conference Room (Box 1)
    - Morishita Jintan/Ume Jintan (Box 1)
    - Otsuka/Olonine Ointment: Pottery of Shigaraki (Box 1)
    - Takeda/Benza (Box 1)
    - Asahi Breweries/Mini-Daru 3: My Favorite Style Pouring (Box 1)
    - Suntory/Suntory Old: China/Peking (Box 1)
    - Suntory/Draft Beer: Elephant (Box 1)
    - Okura Shuzo/Gekkeikan (Sake): Summer (Box 1)
    - Okezi Shuzo/One-Cup Ozeki (Sake): Refrigerator (Box 1)
    - Kirin Brewery Co./Lager Beer: Summer Festival (Box 1)
    - Fujiya Confectionary/Nector: Peach (Box 1)
    - Morinaga Milk Industry/Yogurt: High Tech (Box 1)
    - Kikkoman Shoyu/Del Monte Tomato Juice: U.S. Family (Box 1)
    - Kagome/Kagome Tomato Juice: A Great Black Woodpecker (Box 1)
    - Morinaga/Charmant Chocolate: Sound Effect (Box 1)
    - Culby/Potato Chips: Salt (Box 1)
    - Culby/Kappa Ebisen (rice cracker): Submarine (Box 1)
    - Meiji/My Record: DJ (Box 1)
    - Fujiya Confectionary/Pie Cake: A Mouthful Pie (Box 1)
    - Snow Brand Milk Products/Cream Cheese Cake (Box 1)
    - Yatsuhashi/Hijiri: White Yatsuhashi (Box 1)
    - Morinaga/Buscuit: Conversation (Box 1)
    - Kikkoman Shoyu/Noodle Soup: Keiko (Box 1)
    - Fuji Konbu/Omamesan (cooked beans): Beans and Meat (Box 1)
    - Takara Shuzo/Takara Cooking Sake: Newly on Sale (Box 1)
    - S&B/Mild Golden Curry: Eat More Vegetables (Box 1)
    - Kikkoman Shoyu/Soy sauce for sashimi (Box 1)
    - Morinaga/Morinaga Chiru Chiru (Box 1)
    - Masuko Miso/Yamasa Miso:Mother's Hand (Box 1)
    - Nissin Oil Mills/Salad Oil: Fried Potato (Box 1)
    - Snow Brand Milk Products/Neo Soft (margarine) (Box 1)
    - House Food Industrial/Noodle Rice: Rice and a Smile (Box 1)
    - Ajinomoto/Cook-Do: Tetsuko (Box 1)
    - Ajinomoto/Hi-Me: Oden (Box 1)
    - Momoya/Noodle Soup: The Real Thing (Box 1)
    - Shiseido/Natsuko Pan Cake (Box 1)
    - Shiseido/Benefique Lipstick: Spring (Box 1)
    - Kanebo/Jose Eye Shadow: Blindfold (Box 1)
    - Japan Tobacco & Salt Public Corp./Cabin 85 (Box 1)
    - Kanebo Home Products/Silk Soap: Cooling Off (Box 1)
    - Pilot Pen/Fountain Pen (Box 1)
    - Takashimaya/Rosentar (Box 1)
    - Jyojo Kinbury/Kreenex Tissue: Angel (Box 1)
    - Japan Incense/Incense (Box 1)
    - Lion Fat & Oil Co./Emeron Soap: A Life of a Soap (Box 1)
    - Japan Tobacco & Salt Public Corp./Partner (Box 1)
    - Sasaki Glass: A Shooting Star (Box 1)
    - Lion Fat & Oil Co./Sofran Soap (Box 1)
    - Kubota/Door: Silhouette (Box 1)
    - Tokyo Gas/Air Conditioner: Hustler (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/Hot & Cool (Box 1)
    - Mitsubishi Electric Corp./Clean Heater (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/Refrigerator (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/National Steam Iron (Box 1)
    - Hitachi/Popcorn Maker: Present (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/Neo Hi-Top (Box 1)
    - Marui/Washable Suit (Box 1)
    - Miki/Camellia Diamond: Ginza Jewelry Maki (Box 1)
    - Nippon Kogaku/Nikon Rapid Brown: Poolside (Box 1)
    - Tokai Cotton/Tokai Bedcloth (Box 1)
    - Wacoal/Tammy Girdle 4425: Telephone (Box 1)
    - Yamaha/Tennis Wear (Box 1)
    - Renown/Vassarette Foundation: Body Percussion (Box 1)
    - Daimaru/John Weitz: World of Business (Box 1)
    - Renown/Simple Life: Fish Shop (Box 1)
    - Sanyo Electric Co./Colour TV Set: Foreigner (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/Disco M: Rolling Stones (Box 1)
    - Yamaha/Passage: On the Brooklyn Bridge (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/National Micro Cassette (Box 1)
    - Hitachi/Video Mastax: Names of Railroad Station (Box 1)
    - Toyota/Dina: A Piano Has Come to Our Island (Box 1)
    - Honda/Prelude: Fallen Leaves (Box 1)
    - Bridgestone Tire/Super Filler Radial (Box 1)
    - Casio/Casio Melody: Dokaben (Box 1)
    - Nippon Kogaku/Nikon EM: Lemon (Box 1)
    - Seiko/Watches for Ladies: Ladies (Box 1)
    - Olympic Fishing Tackle/LX 4000 (Box 1)
    - Japan Airline/Fall in Hokkaido: Cinematic Hokkaido (Box 1)
    - Marui/Dolls for the Girls' Festival (Box 1)
    - Japan Airline/JAL pak: I Love New York (Box 1)
    - Ministry of Home Affairs/General Election (Box 1)
    - Idemitsu/Corporate Ad: Tanker (Box 1)
    - Shueish/History of Showa Era (Box 1)
    - Nippon Insurance/Insurance for Everyday Life (Box 1)
    - Nissan Motors/Traffic Safety Campaign (Box 1)
    - Public Advertising Corp./Public Message: Your Words Can Be Weapon (Box 1)
    - Tokyo Electricity/Corporate ad: I Am Electricity (Box 1)
    - Japan Petroleum/Corporate ad: Ceremonial Robe of a Japanese Court Lady (Box 1)
    - Shiseido/Simon Pure: Make-Up for Festival (Box 1)
    - Matsushita Electric Industrial/Electric Range: Japanese Tales (Box 1)
    - International Wool Board/Wool Mark 79: Men's Wear (Box 1)
    - International Wool Board/Wool Mark 79: Carpet (Box 1)
    - International Wool Board/Wool Mark 79: Ladies' Wear (Box 1)
    - Public Advertising Corp./Public Message: Seal Belt Saves Life (Box 1)
    - Public Advertising Corp./Public Message: Why Don't You Put On Seat Belt? (Box 1)
    - Public Advertising Corp./Public Message: Attention Please (Box 1)
    - Marui/Interior (Box 1)
  - 3. Adweek's Best Spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 4. Adweek's Best Spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 5. Adweek's Best Spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 6. Adweek's Best Spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 7. Adweek's Best Spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 8. Adweek's Best Spots. 1987. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 9. A Look At Cable Commercials for Best & Worst of US TV (Copy of a CAS Tape). 1983. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Cheez-Whiz (Box 1)
    - Rice-a-Roni (Box 1)
    - Nelson (Box 1)
    - Kawasaki (Box 1)
    - Camaro (Box 1)
    - Saran Wrap (Box 1)
    - Alpo (Box 1)
  - 10. Award 82 TV Reel. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 1)
  - 11. Awards 83. 1984. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - JVC:Stereo/Headphone (Box 1)
    - ALP:Escalator (Box 1)
    - Portmans: T-Shirts (Box 1)
    - Cerebos: Fountain tomato Sauce (Box 1)
    - Benson & Hedges: One Day Cricket (Box 1)
    - Cheap Jeans: Blue Grass Jan. Sale (Box 1)
    - AAMI: Repairers (Box 1)
    - Dettol Flyers (Box 1)
    - Amatyl: Mt. Franklin Mineral Water (Box 1)
    - Ansett: DC7-DC9 Old/New (Box 1)
    - Commercial Bank: Umbrellas (Box 1)
    - Nestlé: Quik Ballet (Box 1)
    - Harper's: Cat Chow Lobster (Box 1)
    - Harper's: Cat Chow Microphone (Box 1)
    - Electrolux: Broken Light Bulb (Box 1)
    - Berlei Hestia: Sports Bra (Box 1)
    - King Gee: Urn (Box 1)
    - SA FM: Country Cowboy (Box 1)
    - Yalumba: Carte d'Or/Car Door (Box 1)
    - Holeproof corporate (Box 1)
    - Commercial Bank: Bank Manager Yes (Box 1)
    - Kit Kat: Art Gallery (Box 1)
    - State Rail Association: Morning (Box 1)
    - Apple Computer: Younger Men (Box 1)
    - Burger Rings: Star Wars (Box 1)
    - Marantz: Angels (Box 1)
    - Ansett: Dambusters (Box 1)
    - Just Jeans: Street Wise (Box 1)
    - Commericial Bank: Bank Manager campaign (Box 1)
    - State Rail Association: Morning/Freight campaign (Box 1)
    - Harpers: Cat Chow campaign (Box 1)
    - Dr. Bernarto's: Heroin Baby (Box 1)
    - Caption Centre: Two Ronnies (Box 1)
    - Art Gallery: Kev Cavana--Graham Bond (Box 1)
    - NRMA: Drink Driving (Box 1)
    - Suzuki Bikes: Army (Box 1)
    - King Gee: Urn (Box 1)
    - King Gee: Urn (Box 1)
    - Art Gallery: Kev Cavana--Graham Bond (Box 1)
    - Burger Rings: Star Wars (Box 1)
    - AMEX: Mel Blanc (Box 1)
    - AMEX: Robert Ludlum (Box 1)
    - Yalumba: Carte d'Or/Car Door (Box 1)
    - Apple Computer: Younger Men (Box 1)
    - Burger Rings: Star Wars (Box 1)
    - State Rail Association: Campaign (Box 1)
    - BP corporate (Box 1)
    - Thai Airlines: Traditions (Box 1)
    - State Rail Association: Morning (Box 1)
    - Alfa Romeo: Rose (Box 1)
    - Commercial Bank: Manager (Box 1)
    - Apple Computer: Younger Men (Box 1)
    - NSW Art Gallery: Kev Cavana--Graham Bond (Box 1)
    - Bridgestone: Tread (Box 1)
    - Marantz: Angels (Box 1)
    - Benson & Hedges: One Day Cricket (Box 1)
    - Burger Rings: Star Wars (Box 1)
  - 12. Awards 85 Print. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 13. Award Award (Australia). 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 34:00 (Box 1)
  - 14. Award Award (Australia). 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 15. Winners At Work (Australia). 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 1)
  - 16. Winners At Work (Australia). 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 2)
  - 17. Production Houses/Directors: Film Business--David Smith, Julian Castagna, Window, Eureka, Ian McDonald. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 2)
  - 18. Bank Marketing Association, 1979 Best of TV. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - First Wisconsin National Bank of Madison: Teller Training (Box 2)
    - Fidelity American Bank: No Service Charge Checking (Box 2)
    - Rhode Island Hospital Trust National Bank: Butcher Block (Box 2)
    - Interbank Card Associaton (Master Charge): I'm in Charge (Box 2)
    - Banco de Bilbao: Stretch Your Payments (Box 2)
    - Huntington National Bank: Guitar (Box 2)
    - Worthen Bank & Trust Company: French Crystal--Free (Box 2)
    - First National Bank of Atlanta: Silver Platter/Atlanta (Box 2)
    - Harris Bank: Loans (Box 2)
    - Marine Midland Bank: 5 1/2% Good Deal Checking (Box 2)
    - Liberty National Bank: 60 Minute Loan (Box 2)
    - Union Trust Bank: Ask for the Manager (Box 2)
    - Bank of America: Cabbie (Box 2)
    - City National Bank of Baton Rouge: Cash Flow (Box 2)
    - Manufacturers National Bank: Goals (Box 2)
    - Central Pacific Bank: Home Equity Loan (Box 2)
    - Toronto-Dominion Bank: Impressions (Box 2)
    - Fidelity American Bank: What's Inside the Time Machine? (Box 2)
    - Texas Commerce Bank: Chief Executive--Commitment of the Bank (Box 2)
    - Louisiana National Bank: Remember Me (Box 2)
    - Capital National Bank: Emory (Box 2)
    - National Bank of North America: What Will I Choose? (Box 2)
    - New England Merchants National Bank: Shoes (Box 2)
    - Citizens and Southern National Bank: Bounce Protection (Box 2)
    - Maryland National Bank: Bank Card/Waiting (Box 2)
    - Wells Fargo Bank: Fact (Box 2)
    - BancOhio: Well, Well, Well (Box 2)
    - Mellon Bank, N.A.: Really Free Checking (Box 2)
    - United California Bank: $200 Check Guarantee (Box 2)
    - Barclays Bank: Old Faithful (Box 2)
    - Barnett Banks of Florida, Inc.: Some Banks (Box 2)
  - 19. TVB The Bessies Part 1. 1984. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 2)
  - 20. TVB The Bessies Part 2. 1984. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 2)
  - 21. TVB The Bessies Canada, Reel #2. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 2)
  - 22. TVB The Bessies, Reel #1. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 2)
  - 23. 1987 Bessie Awards. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 58:00 (Box 2)
  - 24. Selections for Best & Worst: 10 Calvin Klein, 2 Hanes Pantyhose, 1 Avis Rent-A-Car, 2 Anacin. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 7:30
    - Calvin Klein (10 spots) (Box 2)
    - Hanes Panty Hose (2 spots) (Box 2)
    - Avis (Box 2)
    - Anacin: Patricia Neal (2 spots) (Box 2)
  - 25. 3 I Love New York Commercials for Best & Worst of US TV (from a CAS Copy). Features Elizabeth Taylor, Lauren Bacall, Lena Horne, Brooke Shields, Angela Landsbury, Sandy Duncan.. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:30
    - I Love New York: Elizabeth Taylor/Lauren Bacall/Lena Horne (Box 2)
    - I Love New York: Cats/Brooke Shields (Box 2)
    - I Love New York: Angela Landsbury (Cats)/Sandy Duncan (Peter Pan) (Box 2)
  - 26. The Best Commercials of 1984 (The Television Register). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Philips: Bolero (Box 2)
    - Philips: Breakdance (Box 2)
    - British Airways: Astronauts (Box 2)
    - Nike: England vs. Brazil (Box 2)
    - Quatro: Machine (Box 2)
    - Hamlet Cigars: Olympics (Box 2)
    - Hamlet Cigars: Channel 5 (Box 2)
    - COI: Magpies (Box 2)
    - Sony: Trinitron (Box 2)
    - Dime Bar: Turn the Sound Down (Box 2)
    - British Telecom: Miss Pringle (Box 2)
    - British Telecom: Gunshots (Box 2)
    - Kelly Girl: Metropolis (Box 2)
    - Madame Tussaud's: Arthur Scargill (Box 2)
    - Polo: Straight Down the Middle (Box 2)
    - Dulux Woodsheen: Garden (Box 2)
    - Levi Strauss: Stitching (Box 2)
    - Hofmeister: Footballer (Box 2)
    - BarclayCard: South of France (Box 2)
    - Apple. 1984.: Hammer Thrower (Box 2)
    - Barclay's: Insurance (Box 2)
    - Alex Lawrie Factors: Dog (Box 2)
    - Holstein Pils: Barbara Stanwyck (Box 2)
    - Milton Keynes: Red Balloons (Box 2)
    - Leyland Roadrunner: Brown Trousers (Box 2)
    - Black & Decker: Bride's Headache (Box 2)
    - British Telecom: Quasimodo (Box 2)
    - British Telecom: Neptune (Box 2)
    - British Telecom: Custer (Box 2)
    - Solid Fuel Advisory Committee: Toys (Box 2)
    - Bradford & Bingley: Early Closing (Box 2)
    - ICL: Rugby (Box 2)
    - Addis Housewares: Gallery (Box 2)
    - Cosifits: Refastenable (Box 2)
    - Hamlet: Pink Shiny Dome (Box 2)
    - British Airways: Wider Seats (Box 2)
  - 27. The Best of McCann 1987. 1988. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 14:45
    - American Express: Jacuzzi (Box 2)
    - Isuzu: Tango (Box 2)
    - French's: 9 1/2 Weeks (Box 2)
    - Stefanel Kids: Leisure Wear (Box 2)
    - Shearson: Horses (Box 2)
    - Esso: Ice/Tiger (Box 2)
    - Friskies: Kittens (Box 2)
    - Coca-Cola: Day in the Life (Box 2)
    - Ikea: Day in the Opening (Box 2)
    - Habitat: Chair Baby (Box 2)
    - Californian Milk: The Run (Box 2)
    - P&O: Cruise (Box 2)
    - Waterworld: The Edge (Box 2)
    - Buitoni: The Man I Love (Box 2)
    - Nestlé Quik: Singing in the Rain (Box 2)
    - Gold Blend: Neighbor (Box 2)
    - Gold Blend: Return (Box 2)
    - National Dairy: Late Bloomer (Box 2)
    - Martini Bianco: Sky Screen (Box 2)
    - Drugs: Glamorous World (Box 2)
    - Social: The Informer (Box 2)
  - 28. Video*Ads Cassette #1: The Best U.S. & International Computer Graphics and Animation. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00
    - Levi's: Trademark (Box 2)
    - Wang: Puzzle Pieces (Box 2)
    - Chevrolet Corvette: Never Before (Box 2)
    - 7-Up: Sun Beats Down (Box 2)
    - Bayer Coryfin: Graphics (Box 2)
    - Fruit-of-the-Loom Casual Wear: Taking the Leap (Box 2)
    - Duncan Hines Corn Muffins: Tickle the Noses (Box 2)
    - Levi's: Countdown (Box 2)
    - Mattel Electronics: Tron (Box 2)
    - Zaxxon (Saga) (Box 2)
    - Marantz: Hear No Evil (Box 2)
    - TRW: Changing Picture (Box 2)
    - Suzuki Tempter: The Sensation (Box 2)
    - Maxfli DDH: Take Your Game (Box 2)
    - Meqquiar's Auto Wax (Box 2)
    - Lois: Pop Dancers (Box 2)
    - Dulux: The White Shades of PAL. e (Box 2)
    - Fresh Cream Cakes: Mona Lisa (Box 2)
    - TSB: Graphics (Box 2)
    - Fabergé Jeans: The World Today (Box 2)
    - Moove Flavored Milk: Fantasy (Box 2)
    - Pennzoil: Protection (Box 2)
    - Norelco Rototrack (Box 2)
    - Tropicana: 5 Miles that Sizzle (Box 2)
    - Sensodyne Search Tooth Brush (Box 2)
    - Zenith TV: The Smart Set (Box 2)
    - Western Electric: Olympics (Box 2)
    - Bamerindos Bank: Dream (Box 2)
    - Ben Truman Beer: Change (Box 2)
    - Dispirin: Bear (Box 2)
    - Right Guard: Long Noses (Box 2)
    - Twice as Fresh Air Freshener: Computer Game (Box 2)
    - Limara Perfume: Sleeping Beauty (Box 2)
    - HP All Sauce: Mrs. Hickerbacker (Box 2)
    - Breville Sandwich Toaster: Crying Sandwich (Box 2)
    - Post: Flying Carpet (Box 2)
    - Chokito Candy: Pop Art (Box 2)
    - Oxy 10/5: Pimples Packing (Box 2)
    - Heinz Salad Cream: Talking Plate (Box 2)
    - Silver Creek Tobacco: Follow the Creek (Box 2)
    - Triple M Radion Station: Triple Your Music (Box 2)
    - WAPP Radio Station: Rocking the Apple (Box 2)
    - Pioneer Auto Stereo: Solar Colors (Box 2)
  - 29. British Advertising Broadcast Awards, Reel #1. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 56:00 (Box 2)
  - 30. British Advertising Broadcast Awards, Reel #2. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 45:00 (Box 2)
  - 31. British Advertising Broadcast Awards, Reel #3. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 3)
  - 32. The Best of British. 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 15:00
    - Volvo: Ice Cube (Box 3)
    - British Airways: Wider Seats (Box 3)
    - Citroën: Tortoise (Box 3)
    - British Rail: Plane to Train (Box 3)
    - Diat Pils Lager: Barbara Stanwyck (Box 3)
    - Heineken: B Movie (Box 3)
    - Radio Rentals: Wuthering Heights (Box 3)
    - Creda: Baby (Box 3)
    - Creda: Darts (Box 3)
    - Philips: Bolero (Box 3)
    - Dulux: Art Gallery (Box 3)
    - Telecom: Custer (Box 3)
    - Telecom: Hunchback (Box 3)
    - Hofmeister: Sportsman (Box 3)
    - Crime Prevention: Magpies (Box 3)
    - Solid Fuel: Toys (Box 3)
    - Cosifits: Perpetual Motion (Box 3)
    - Hamlet: Wig (Box 3)
    - Hamlet: Olympics (Box 3)
    - Toshiba: FST (Box 3)
    - Sony: Lifespan (Box 3)
    - John Smith's: Exercise (Box 3)
    - John Smith's: True Love (Box 3)
    - John Smith's: The Wrong Crowd (Box 3)
    - John Smith's: Song and Dance (Box 3)
  - 33. The Best of British. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 15:00 (Box 3)
  - 34. 1985 British TV Advertising Awards. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Kiri: Apple with Sparkler (Box 3)
    - Castlemaine XXXX: Flying Doctor (Box 3)
    - Cosifits: Perpetual Motion (Box 3)
    - Trio: Suzy (Box 3)
    - Toshiba Television: FST (Box 3)
    - Philips: Bolero (Box 3)
    - Citroën 2CV: Tortoise (Box 3)
    - Audi Coupe: Bank (Box 3)
    - Barclays Bank: Mr. Grey (Box 3)
    - Radio Rentals: Beau Geste (Box 3)
    - Kelly Girls: Metropolis (Box 3)
    - British Airways: Wider Seats (Box 3)
    - British Rail: Plane to Train (Box 3)
    - Clark Shoes: Baby Plant (Box 3)
    - Running: Tortoise (Box 3)
    - Rank Xerox: Statman (Box 3)
    - British Telecom: Quotation (Box 3)
    - Heineken Lager: B-Awful B-Movie (Box 3)
    - Volvo 340DL: Ice Cube (Box 3)
    - Apple Computer: Lemmings (Box 3)
    - Hamlet Cigars: Pink Shiny Dome/Olympics (Box 3)
    - Creda: Wed Monday/Baby/Darts (Box 3)
    - Toshiba: Hi-fi (Box 3)
    - Philips: Breakdance (Box 3)
    - Radio Rentals: Love Scene (Box 3)
    - Solid Fuel: Toys (Box 3)
    - Crime Prevention: Magpies (Box 3)
    - Pepsi Cola: Spaceship (Box 3)